<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/</link><description>Recent content on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://ct-products.cz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Offshore containers</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/products/offshore-containers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/products/offshore-containers/</guid><description>We produce special containers and equipment intended for petroleum industry. The containers are of the “offshore” type which means they are certified according to respective standards for reloading on an open sea.
We perform two types of testing Production test Production test where the primary structure of the container is tested for the required load (up to 100 tons) and the container is gripped at 2 or 4 points.
Prototype testing Prototype test, in particular the fall test, where the primary structure of the prototype is dropped from a special hinge to the ground.</description></item><item><title>Welding</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/technology/welding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/technology/welding/</guid><description>We ensure welding and inspection processes according to ISO 3834-2. MIG, MAG (131, 135), TIG (141)
Qualification of workers for welding Welding is performed by trained welding personnel with a valid examination according to ČSN EN ISO 9606-1 for the respective welding method at the given quality degree according to ČSN EN 5817. International welding engineer (IWE) in our team.
Non-destructive testing We perform visual test according to ČSN EN ISO 17637 Magnetic test according to ČSN EN ISO 17638 Ultrasound test according to ČSN EN ISO 17640</description></item><item><title>Cargo chasis trailers</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/products/cargo-chasis-trailers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/products/cargo-chasis-trailers/</guid><description>At our engineering company, we use only the highest quality carbon steel in the production of our cargo chassis trailers. Our skilled engineers and technicians work diligently to ensure that every step of the production process is carried out to the highest standards. We use state-of-the-art equipment to cut, shape, and weld the steel, ensuring that each trailer is built to last.</description></item><item><title>Laser cutting</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/technology/laser-cutting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/technology/laser-cutting/</guid><description>Laser Genius+ 2040 6kW, PRIMA POWER Material Maximum thickness Construction steel 25mm Stainless steel 25mm Aluminium 25mm Copper 10mm Brass 10mm</description></item><item><title>Assemblies</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/technology/assemblies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/technology/assemblies/</guid><description>Besides classical engineering production, we offer our clients the production of all cooperation parts and consequent installation in complete assemblies of finished product.</description></item><item><title>Stainless steel products</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/products/stainless-steel-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/products/stainless-steel-products/</guid><description>We have top quality welding and metal-working machines in the field of the stainless steel production. We emphasize the quality of workmanship. By using our laser cutting machine and CNC press brake, we can offer producing precise metal sheet parts and engineering units for various industrial sectors.</description></item><item><title>Engineering</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/products/engineering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/products/engineering/</guid><description>We offer our customers the production from simple burnouts on our laser cutting machine including bending, welding and surface treatment, up to the delivery of complicated weldment units including machining and consequent assembly. We are able to weld steel structures up to the weight of 5000 kg.</description></item><item><title>Press brake and roll bending</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/technology/press-brake-roll-bending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/technology/press-brake-roll-bending/</guid><description>Specification of SAFAN Darley</description></item><item><title>Assembly</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/products/assembly/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/products/assembly/</guid><description>In cooperation with our long-term partners we provide all the following operations including mechanical and electrical assemblies or assembling of products according to the submitted documentation. We also ensure assembling large units, and we assemble highly precise smaller mechanical parts of machines. We perform consequent assembly and installation of various equipment to containers.</description></item><item><title>Machining</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/technology/machining/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/technology/machining/</guid><description>Milling machine VMCA 1000 CNC Lifting capacity table Dimension of table Spindle 800 kg 1520 x 520 mm 10 000 rev/min Turning machine SA 48/1000 CNC Maximum turning length Maximum workpiece weight Spindle 1000 mm 1500 kg 100 - 4500 rev/min</description></item><item><title>About us</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/company/aboutus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/company/aboutus/</guid><description/></item><item><title>History of company</title><link>http://ct-products.cz/company/history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ct-products.cz/company/history/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>