<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/</link><description>Recent content on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ct-products.cz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Offshore containers</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/products/offshore-containers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/products/offshore-containers/</guid><description>We produce special containers and equipment intended for petroleum industry. The containers are of the “offshore” type which means they are certified according to respective standards for reloading on an open sea.
We perform two types of testing Production test Production test where the primary structure of the container is tested for the required load (up to 100 tons) and the container is gripped at 2 or 4 points.
Prototype test Prototype test, in particular the fall test, where the primary structure of the prototype is dropped from a special hinge to the ground.</description></item><item><title>Welding</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/welding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/welding/</guid><description>We are dedicated to delivering welding and inspection processes that adhere to the stringent standards of ISO 3834-2. Our commitment to excellence is reflected in our use of advanced techniques, including MIG (131), MAG (135), and TIG (141). From concept to creation, our metal fabrication services cover a wide spectrum, including structural steel, aluminum, and stainless steel fabrication. We understand that each project is unique. That&amp;rsquo;s why International Welding Engineer (IWE) is an integral part of our team.</description></item><item><title>Cargo chasis trailers</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/products/cargo-chasis-trailers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/products/cargo-chasis-trailers/</guid><description>Our additional long-standing expertise lies in the production of cargo trailers. Here, we excel in collaboration with our customers by processing our own technical documentation. Typically, in this sector, we deal with small-batch production. We are capable of working with high-strength and wear-resistant quenched steels, such as S600 MC, Weldox 900, and others. Subsequently, in this field, we have implemented our own automated process for welding long seams. We manufacture trailers of various lengths, ranging from 8 m to 16 m.</description></item><item><title>Welding automation</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/welding-automation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/welding-automation/</guid><description>CTP 1350 We delveloped device for welding long welds. The device is mainly desinged for welding long welds of fillet welds and butt welds by methods MIG or MAG. Advantages of this device is simultaneous welding from two sides. Its main components consist of a support frame with a longitudinal positioning table for workpieces and a horizontal linear track with a traversing carriage. This track includes a carriage drive, wire feeders, welding torches, technological torches with vertical and horizontal correction supports, welding torch holders, and a control unit.</description></item><item><title>Laser cutting</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/laser-cutting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/laser-cutting/</guid><description>Laser Genius+ 2040 6kW, PRIMA POWER Material Maximum thickness Construction steel 25mm Stainless steel 25mm Aluminium 25mm Copper 10mm Brass 10mm</description></item><item><title>Stainless steel products</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/products/stainless-steel-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/products/stainless-steel-products/</guid><description>One of the three pillars of our production is focused on welding stainless steel. Our dedicated workshop enables us to weld smaller, lighter weldments compared to the production of containers or trailers. Here, we have experience in manufacturing food industry structures, pipes, tanks, and various other welded components. In this field, we have also encountered heat-resistant stainless steels.</description></item><item><title>Press brake and roll bending</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/press-brake-roll-bending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/press-brake-roll-bending/</guid><description>Specification of SAFAN Darley</description></item><item><title>Machining</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/machining/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/machining/</guid><description>Milling machine VMCA 1000 CNC Lifting capacity table Dimension of table Spindle 800 kg 1520 x 520 mm 10 000 rev/min Turning machine SA 48/1000 CNC Maximum turning length Maximum workpiece weight Spindle 1000 mm 1500 kg 100 - 4500 rev/min</description></item><item><title>Other products</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/products/other-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/products/other-products/</guid><description>Explore the gallery of our other products. In the gallery, you will find countless products, using individual technologies and their combinations. We offer single sheet metal parts, bent sheet metal parts, weldments, machined parts, assembled units. We also are capable to weld alumiunim parts.</description></item><item><title>Assemblies and products testing</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/assemblies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/assemblies/</guid><description>Besides classical engineering production, we offer our clients the production of all cooperation parts and consequent installation in complete assemblies of finished product.</description></item><item><title>Engineering</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/engineering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/engineering/</guid><description>We offer our customers the production from simple burnouts on our laser cutting machine including bending, welding and surface treatment, up to the delivery of complicated weldment units including machining and consequent assembly. We are able to weld steel structures up to the weight of 5000 kg.</description></item><item><title>Blasting</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/blasting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/blasting/</guid><description>We perform glass blasting of stainless steel</description></item><item><title>About us</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/company/aboutus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/company/aboutus/</guid><description/></item><item><title>History of company</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/company/history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/company/history/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>