<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mechanical Engineering on Home</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/tags/mechanical-engineering/</link><description>Recent content in Mechanical Engineering on Home</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ct-products.cz/tags/mechanical-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Other products</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/products/other-products/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/products/other-products/</guid><description>Explore the gallery of our other products. In the gallery, you will find countless products, using individual technologies and their combinations. We offer single sheet metal parts, bent sheet metal parts, weldments, machined parts, assembled units. We also are capable to weld aluminium parts.</description></item><item><title>Engineering</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/engineering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/engineering/</guid><description>The company is capable of processing the necessary technical documentation, such as reading and understanding manufacturing drawings. It can also handle 3D models, utilizing Solid Edge 2019 software for this purpose. The team consists of skilled individuals who are not afraid to take on projects. They can work even with less than perfect technical documentation. If needed, they can redraw manufacturing drawings for their production needs and choose the simplest and most cost-effective manufacturing technology.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/contact/</guid><description>Get in touch with us</description></item><item><title>Our products</title><link>https://ct-products.cz/products/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ct-products.cz/products/</guid><description>Our products are designed with precision, durability, and functionality in mind. We offer a wide range of custom-engineered solutions tailored to meet the specific needs of our clients. With a focus on quality and innovation, we ensure that every product meets the highest industry standards. Serving various industries, including oil and gas, automotive, clean tech, agriculture, and more, our diverse portfolio demonstrates our ability to adapt to different sector requirements.</description></item></channel></rss>