<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Metals on Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:61221/tags/metals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Metals on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:61221/tags/metals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61221/technology/welding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:61221/technology/welding/</guid>
      <description>We are dedicated to delivering welding and inspection processes that adhere to the stringent standards of ISO 3834-2. Our commitment to excellence is reflected in our use of advanced techniques, including MIG (131), MAG (135), and TIG (141). From concept to creation, our metal fabrication services cover a wide spectrum, including structural steel, aluminium, and stainless steel fabrication. We understand that each project is unique. That&amp;rsquo;s why International Welding Engineer (IWE) is an integral part of our team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laser cutting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61221/technology/laser-cutting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:61221/technology/laser-cutting/</guid>
      <description>Laser Genius+ 2040 6kW, PRIMA POWER, (Fiber technology) Laser Genius+ is combined with the new fiber laser head, new electronics and innovative mounting for the optics and centering system, guarantee a maximum level of precision and cutting quality.&#xA;Parameters Value Axis strokes X: 4 320 mm, Y: 2 200 mm, Z: 150 mm Laser power 6 000 W (max. thickness of standard steel, stainless steel and aluminium is 25 mm) Maximum piece weight 2000kg Positioning accuracy and repeatability X, Y: 0,03 mm Speed 130/min (trajectory 180m/min) Acceleration 2,8 g </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press brake and roll bending</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61221/technology/press-brake-roll-bending/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:61221/technology/press-brake-roll-bending/</guid>
      <description>Safan E-Brake B 100-3100 The E-Brake incorporates all the benefits of the proven servo-electric drive concept. The transfer of pressing force relies on a mechanism with flat belts and a set of rotating wheels on roller bearings. Thanks to incomparably higher acceleration and deceleration of the ram, it achieves greater productivity compared to hydraulic presses.&#xA;Parameters Value Maximum bending force 1 000 kN Maximum working length 3 100 mm BENDMAK | CY SERIES 3-ROLL Intial pinch plate rolls The Bendmak CY Series 3 Roll Initial Pinch style of plate rolls are the most popular style for thinner material requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machining</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61221/technology/machining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:61221/technology/machining/</guid>
      <description>In the context of our manufacturing operations a milling machine and a lathe offer support. These tools empower us to adapt flexibly to the requirements of our primary welding production.&#xA;Milling machine Microcut VMCA 1000 CNC Parameters Value Traverses: X: 1 000 mm, Y: 500 mm, Z: 500 mm Table: 1520 x 520 mm Spindle speed: 10 000 rpm Turning machine SA 48/1000 CNC Parameters Value Max. swing diameter, without bed bridge: 710 mm Swing diameter over bed: 475 mm Max.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
