<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on Home</title>
    <link>https://ct-products.cz/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ct-products.cz/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welding</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/welding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/welding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are dedicated to delivering welding and inspection processes that adhere to the stringent standards of ISO 3834-2. Our commitment to excellence is reflected in our use of advanced techniques, including MIG (131), MAG (135), and TIG (141).&#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; &#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;From concept to creation, our metal fabrication services cover a wide spectrum, including structural steel, aluminium, and stainless steel fabrication.&#xA;We understand that each project is unique. That&amp;rsquo;s why International Welding Engineer (IWE) is an integral part of our team. Their proficiency and knowledge contribute to the continuous enhancement of our welding processes, making us a reliable partner for projects that demand precision and international standards.&#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; &#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Our team comprises qualified welding personnel who bring a wealth of expertise to every project, ensuring accuracy and reliability in every weld.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welding automation</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/welding-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/welding-automation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We developed device for welding long welds. The device is mainly designed for welding long welds of fillet welds and butt welds by methods MIG or MAG. Advantages of this device is simultaneous welding from two sides. Its main components consist of a support frame with a longitudinal positioning table for workpieces and a horizontal linear track with a traversing carriage. This track includes a carriage drive, wire feeders, welding torches, technological torches with vertical and horizontal correction supports, welding torch holders, and a control unit. The welding process is operated by two remote control joysticks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laser cutting</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/laser-cutting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/laser-cutting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h6 id=&#34;laser-genius-2040-6kw-prima-power-fiber-technology&#34;&gt;Laser Genius+ 2040 6kW, PRIMA POWER, (Fiber technology)&lt;/h6&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Laser Genius+ is combined with the new fiber laser head, new electronics and innovative mounting for the optics and centering system, guarantee a maximum level of precision and cutting quality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Parameters&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Axis strokes&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;X: 4 320 mm, Y: 2 200 mm, Z: 150 mm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Laser power&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;6 000 W (max. thickness of standard steel, stainless steel and aluminium is 25 mm)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Maximum piece weight&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2000kg&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Positioning accuracy and repeatability&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;X, Y: 0,03 mm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Speed&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;130/min (trajectory 180m/min)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Acceleration&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2,8 g&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stainless steel products</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/products/stainless-steel-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/products/stainless-steel-products/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the three pillars of our production is focused on welding stainless steel. Our dedicated workshop enables us to weld smaller, lighter weldments compared to the production of containers or trailers. Here, we have experience in manufacturing food industry structures, pipes, tanks, and various other welded components. In this field, we have also encountered heat-resistant stainless steels.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other products</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/products/other-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/products/other-products/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Explore the gallery of our other products. In the gallery, you will find countless products, using individual technologies and their combinations. We offer single sheet metal parts, bent sheet metal parts, weldments, machined parts, assembled units. We also are capable to weld aluminium parts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press brake and roll bending</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/press-brake-roll-bending/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/press-brake-roll-bending/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h6 id=&#34;safan-e-brake-b-100-3100&#34;&gt;Safan E-Brake B 100-3100&lt;/h6&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The E-Brake incorporates all the benefits of the proven servo-electric drive concept. The transfer of pressing force relies on a mechanism with flat belts and a set of rotating wheels on roller bearings. Thanks to incomparably higher acceleration and deceleration of the ram, it achieves greater productivity compared to hydraulic presses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Parameters&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Maximum bending force&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;1 000 kN&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Maximum working length&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;3 100 mm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;h6 id=&#34;bendmak--cy-series-3-roll-intial-pinch-plate-rolls&#34;&gt;BENDMAK | CY SERIES 3-ROLL Intial pinch plate rolls&lt;/h6&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Bendmak CY Series 3 Roll Initial Pinch style of plate rolls are the most popular style for thinner material requirements. Asymmetrical design allows the sheet metal to be correctly aligned before bending. With the sheet metal properly clamped between two rolls during forming it ensures the material maintains its position guaranteeing precise bending.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machining</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/machining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/machining/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the context of our manufacturing operations a milling machine and a lathe offer support. These tools empower us to adapt flexibly to the requirements of our primary welding production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h6 id=&#34;milling-machine-microcut-vmca-1000-cnc&#34;&gt;Milling machine Microcut VMCA 1000 CNC&lt;/h6&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Parameters&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Traverses:&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;X: 1 000 mm, Y: 500 mm, Z: 500 mm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Table:&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;1520 x 520 mm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Spindle speed:&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;10 000 rpm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;h6 id=&#34;turning-machine-sa-481000--cnc&#34;&gt;Turning machine SA 48/1000  CNC&lt;/h6&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Parameters&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Max. swing diameter, without bed bridge:&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;710 mm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Swing diameter over bed:&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;475 mm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Max. turning length:&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;1 000 mm&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Max. workpiece weight:&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;1 000 kg&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/engineering/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The company is capable of processing the necessary technical documentation, such as reading and understanding manufacturing drawings. It can also handle 3D models, utilizing Solid Edge 2019 software for this purpose. The team consists of skilled individuals who are not afraid to take on projects. They can work even with less than perfect technical documentation. If needed, they can redraw manufacturing drawings for their production needs and choose the simplest and most cost-effective manufacturing technology. In exceptional cases, the company may also provide design proposals for constructions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our products</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/products/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our products are designed with precision, durability, and functionality in mind. We offer a wide range of custom-engineered solutions tailored to meet the specific needs of our clients. With a focus on quality and innovation, we ensure that every product meets the highest industry standards.&#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; &#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Serving various industries, including oil and gas, automotive, clean tech, agriculture, and more, our diverse portfolio demonstrates our ability to adapt to different sector requirements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technology</title>
      <link>https://ct-products.cz/technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ct-products.cz/technology/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our company utilizes advanced technologies to ensure precision, efficiency, and innovation in every project. From cutting-edge machining to state-of-the-art fabrication processes, our expertise allows us to deliver high-quality, custom-engineered solutions that meet the most demanding requirements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
